<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
    <channel>
        <title>Gadgets | Technically Dope</title>
        <description>Gadget by Dope-T-Rope is a Spin-off from Dopetrope project particularly ...</description>
        <link>https://gadgets.dopetrope.tk/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://gadgets.dopetrope.tk/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 07:08:42 +0530</pubDate>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 07:08:42 +0530</lastBuildDate>
        <generator>Jekyll v3.8.7</generator>
        
        <item>
            <title>The POCO M2 Pro may be another POCO smartphone with a mid-range processor</title>
            <description>POCO M2 Pro spotted on certification websites</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Shortly after the launch of the POCO X2 earlier this year, we learned that a new POCO phone was in the works. However, we knew it to be a flagship device called the POCO F2 Pro which would essentially be a rebranded version of the Redmi K30 Pro. But we now have evidence to believe that the POCO F2 Pro isn’t the only device that the company is working on right now and it may soon launch another mid-range device.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A new device, called the POCO M2 Pro, was recently spotted on the Mi India website, in the section where...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 18:46:29 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://gadgets.dopetrope.tk/the-poco-m2-pro-may-be-another-poco-smartphone-with-a-mid-range-processor/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://gadgets.dopetrope.tk/the-poco-m2-pro-may-be-another-poco-smartphone-with-a-mid-range-processor/</guid>
            <category>xiaomi</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Realme X50 Pro 5G Review – Value Flagship Smartphone for 2020</title>
            <description>its uniqueness lies in the front-facing camera</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;The smartphone market has taken many unexpected turns in 2020 – and that’s without getting into any of the ramifications of the currently-ongoing worldwide COVID-19 pandemic. We’ve seen the advent of the Qualcomm Snapdragon 865 and the adoption of 5G drive flagship smartphone prices sky-high, with the most recent additions to the OnePlus lineup continuing the trend of an upwardly increasing starting price. On top of that, we’ve seen rumors that the Google Pixel 5 may be the first in the company’s lineup to not feature the latest flagship chipset from Qualcomm.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The higher cost of flagship smartphones in 2020...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 18:37:14 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://gadgets.dopetrope.tk/realme-x50-pro-5g-review-value-flagship-smartphone-for-2020/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://gadgets.dopetrope.tk/realme-x50-pro-5g-review-value-flagship-smartphone-for-2020/</guid>
            <category>xiaomi</category>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Welcome to Gadgets by Dopetrope</title>
            <description>A Spin-off Website from Dopetrope for Gadget News</description>
            <content:encoded>&lt;h5 id=&quot;about-gadgets-by-dopetrope&quot;&gt;About - Gadgets by Dopetrope&lt;/h5&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*Gadgets by Dopetrope&lt;/strong&gt; is a ambitious Project Found For Sharing Tech News and Updates from various Tech Sources and Blogs.*&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*Gadgets by Dopetrope&lt;/strong&gt; Posts Various News From Popular Sources and it is constantly improving in terms of Technical Competence and also in terms of Content Quality. Currently dopetrope is Posting various News from various Sources. It is Also Constantly Improving in terms of Providing Original Content*&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The latest tech news about the world’s best (and sometimes worst) hardware, apps, and much more. From top companies like Google and Apple to tiny startups vying for...</content:encoded>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 15:59:46 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>https://gadgets.dopetrope.tk/welcome-to-gadgets-by-dopetrope/</link>
            <dc:creator>Sudharshan TK</dc:creator>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://gadgets.dopetrope.tk/welcome-to-gadgets-by-dopetrope/</guid>
            <category>misc</category>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>

